# VINCENZO IEVA

Date of birth: 13/09/1988 Telephone: 07405497738
London, N7 7RD E-mail: vincenzo ieva@hotmail.it

# Professional profile & Career goal

I demonstrate excellent team working skills and enjoy working in dynamic environments where learning is key to success. I have over 4 years of exposure on Web Analytics, however I keep studying try to enrich my knowledge and my skills. From web analytics to coding I try to learn as much as I can to become more efficient and effective in my work environment but also to satisfy my thirst for knowledge.

## Work experience

Nov 2019- present Senior Web Analyst for FMPX

# Oct 2018-Nov 2018 Senior Web Analyst for DMPG

- Reporting using all Adobe Analytics tools
- Web analytics for App tracking implementation
- Using Python to automate basic manual daily processes
- Tag Migration
- Tag analysis via Dynamic Tag manager and Tealium
- Analytics audit of client website

# Jan 2017-Sept 2018 Web Analyst for Station10

- Reporting using all Adobe Analytics tools and Google Analytics
- Analytics audit of client website (from debugging to report suite configuration)
- Using Python to automate basic manual daily processes
- Tag analysis via Dynamic Tag manager and <u>GTM</u>
- Dashboarding using DOMO, (certified)

## May 2016-Jan 2017

# Web Analyst for The Telegraph Media Group

- Reporting using all Adobe Analytics tools.
- Building dashboards by connecting BigQuery and Tableau
- Using Python to automate basic manual daily processes
- Tag analysis via Dynamic Tag manager

## June2015-April 2016

## Web Analyst for Starcom Mediavest

- Providing insights to my client using Google Analytics Premium and Double Click to build a better picture of the website users;
- Attribution Model built to find out display campaign contribution;
- Optimization of metrics and dimensions using GTM;
- User experience analysis for Samsung using Adobe Analytics.

## Marketing & Sales support for London Financial Studies, London

- Cross-selling project management;
- Generating leads for the sales force;
- Direct email marketing support;
- Sales analysis for EMEA, AMERICA and ASIA PAC;
- Marketing analysis using VBA, SQL, Excel and GA.

Pagina 1 di 2 Curriculum vitae of Vincenzo Ieva

#### September 2013 - August 2014

Marketing Assistant, Aesthetic&Corrective Business for Galderma (Nestlè group), Milan.

- Building report and analysis on demand by using Excel;
- Implementing 2 app projects for division's sales force;
- Designing marketing projects aiming to increase products awareness;
- Cooperating with the Digital Marketing Manager in managing social media activities;
- Analyzing and monitoring the market.
- Promotional material translations, graphic creation of congress materials, managing the press release;

## Education and Qualifications

#### 2010-2012

UNIVERSITY of PAVIA - Faculty of Economics,

Master degree in Management and international business of economics

- Level classification of 107/110.
- Master Thesis: "The relationship between ownership and performance: an empirical analysis of the Italian market".

#### 2008 - 2010

UNIVERSITY of PAVIA - Faculty of Economics,

Bachelor degree in Management and administration

- Level classification of 98/110
- Final dissertation about quality control: "Six- Sigma method".

# **Educational Experience Abroad**

# August2011 - January2012 University of Vaasa, Finland

As Exchange student I lived in Vaasa, where I experienced the typical Finnish lifestyle.

# August2010

## Randolph School of English, Edinburgh(UK)

I experienced a month in Edinburgh, where I lived with a Scottish family while attending English courses to improve my skills.

## Additional skills

## Mother tongue: Italian

	English	Spanish	French
Reading	Excellent	Good	Good
Writing	Excellent	Moderate	Moderate
Speaking	Excellent	Good	Sufficient
Listening	Excellent	Good	Good

## IT skills

Certified by Google both from Google Analytics and Adwords. DOMO certified.

Excellent knowledge of Microsoft Office. My computer skills in Excel, Word and PowerPoint have evolved thanks to daily use at work. In addition I use every day other program like: Goldmine, Sendblaster, Python, Javascript, CSS, Adobe stack and Google Stack. Trained during my studies in using **Stata**.

# Pagina 2 di 2